{
  "question_papers": [
    {
      "title": "Vedic Math (SAN) -- Practice Paper 1",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "vedic",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n612",
          "answer": 388
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n179",
          "answer": 821
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n173",
          "answer": 827
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n484",
          "answer": 516
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n104",
          "answer": 896
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n687 x 5",
          "answer": 3435
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n756 x 5",
          "answer": 3780
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n6804 x 5",
          "answer": 34020
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n2347 x 5",
          "answer": 11735
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n7256 x 5",
          "answer": 36280
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n6382 x 25",
          "answer": 159550
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n6882 x 25",
          "answer": 172050
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n5793 x 25",
          "answer": 144825
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n8944 x 25",
          "answer": 223600
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n486342 x 25",
          "answer": 12158550
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n7654 x 125",
          "answer": 956750
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n3271 x 125",
          "answer": 408875
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n7282 x 125",
          "answer": 910250
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n8657 x 125",
          "answer": 1082125
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n1073 x 125",
          "answer": 134125
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n68 x 62",
          "answer": 4216
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n76 x 74",
          "answer": 5624
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n95 x 95",
          "answer": 9025
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n19 x 11",
          "answer": 209
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n38 x 32",
          "answer": 1216
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n12 x 92",
          "answer": 1104
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n52 x 52",
          "answer": 2704
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n24 x 84",
          "answer": 2016
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n10 x 90",
          "answer": 900
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n73 x 33",
          "answer": 2409
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n7.3 x 7.7",
          "answer": 56.21
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n1.6 x 1.4",
          "answer": 2.24
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n9.3 x 9.7",
          "answer": 90.21
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n4.7 x 4.3",
          "answer": 20.21
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n3.9 x 3.1",
          "answer": 12.09
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n8",
          "answer":2
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n5",
          "answer":5
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n2",
          "answer":8
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n7",
          "answer":3
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n6",
          "answer":4
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n4",
          "answer":5
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n1",
          "answer":8
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n3",
          "answer":6
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n9",
          "answer":0
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n7",
          "answer":2
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Vedic Math",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "vedic",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\na) 98 + 9 + 8",
          "answer": 113
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\nb) 79 + 68 + 8",
          "answer": 155
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\nc) 26 + 88 + 9",
          "answer": 123
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\nd) 87 + 29 + 8",
          "answer": 124
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\ne) 18 + 7 + 8",
          "answer": 33
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\nf) 49 + 9 + 7",
          "answer": 65
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\ng) 378 + 89 + 77",
          "answer": 545
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\nh) 898 + 196 + 79",
          "answer": 1173
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\ni) 298 + 787 + 298",
          "answer": 1483
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\nj) 587 + 789 + 679",
          "answer": 2055
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n6.9 + 3.8 + 0.8 + 0.9 + 1.5",
          "answer": 13.9
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n4.5 + 6.3 + 7.8 + 9.5 + 3.2",
          "answer": 31.3
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n9.4 + 5.1 + 4.3 + 2.1 + 3.4",
          "answer": 24.3
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n8.2 + 5.1 + 4.3 + 4.5 + 7.3",
          "answer": 29.4
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n5.6 + 7.2 + 0.9 + 1.3 + 1.8",
          "answer": 16.8
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n2.45 + 9.65 + 0.24 + 2.97 + 1.42",
          "answer": 16.73
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n4.75 + 3.06 + 1.73 + 3.22 + 1.27",
          "answer": 14.03
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n7.57 + 7.23 + 4.33 + 3.33 + 2.33",
          "answer": 24.79
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n5.53 + 2.32 + 5.54 + 4.13 + 1.41",
          "answer": 16.93
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n1.80 + 0.15 + 2.41 + 4.28 + 0.10",
          "answer": 8.74
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n3221 - 1763",
          "answer": 1458
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n5612 - 3787",
          "answer": 1825
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n8191 - 6392",
          "answer": 1799
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n7427 - 1631",
          "answer": 5796
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n6249 - 4679",
          "answer": 1570
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n4513 - 1514",
          "answer": 2999
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n8563 - 2871",
          "answer": 5692
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n32446 - 15879",
          "answer": 16567
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n98634 - 78997",
          "answer": 19637
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n31368 - 13889",
          "answer": 17479
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n62 x 11",
          "answer": 682
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n43 x 11",
          "answer": 473
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n93 x 11",
          "answer": 1023
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n831 x 11",
          "answer": 9141
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n186 x 11",
          "answer": 2046
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n5412 x 11",
          "answer": 59532
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n7628 x 11",
          "answer": 83908
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n1768 x 11",
          "answer": 19448
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n9881 x 11",
          "answer": 108691
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n6153 x 11",
          "answer": 67683
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Vedic Math (G)",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "vedic",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 37",
          "answer": 963
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 284",
          "answer": 716
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 756",
          "answer": 244
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 894",
          "answer": 106
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 864",
          "answer": 136
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 864",
          "answer": 136
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 595",
          "answer": 405
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 785",
          "answer": 215
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n10000 - 9897",
          "answer": 103
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n10000 - 7274",
          "answer": 2726
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n10000 - 8376",
          "answer": 1624
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n37 + 8",
          "answer": 45
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n89 + 8",
          "answer": 97
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n49 + 5",
          "answer": 54
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n98 + 6",
          "answer": 104
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n59 + 7",
          "answer": 66
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n84 + 33",
          "answer": 117
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n89 + 56",
          "answer": 145
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n49 + 78",
          "answer": 127
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n97 + 89",
          "answer": 186
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n89 + 82",
          "answer": 171
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n25/19",
          "answer": 269
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n39/24",
          "answer": 414
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n16/07",
          "answer": 167
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n19/17",
          "answer": 207
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n29/83",
          "answer": 373
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n15/14/13",
          "answer": 1653
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n12/33/07",
          "answer": 1537
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n48/12/12",
          "answer": 4992
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n85/23/56",
          "answer": 8886
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n14/08/15",
          "answer": 1495
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n12 x 14",
          "answer": 168
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n17 x 18",
          "answer": 306
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n13 x 17",
          "answer": 221
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n18 x 18",
          "answer": 324
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n15 x 14",
          "answer": 210
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n11 x 17",
          "answer": 187
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n19 x 19",
          "answer": 361
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n16 x 19",
          "answer": 304
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n17 x 12",
          "answer": 204
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n16 x 11",
          "answer": 176
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Vedic Math (G) Practice Paper 2",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "vedic",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n100 - 72",
          "answer": 28
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 875",
          "answer": 125
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 655",
          "answer": 345
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 725",
          "answer": 275
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n1000 - 675",
          "answer": 325
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n10000 - 8975",
          "answer": 1025
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n10000 - 3279",
          "answer": 6721
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n10000 - 5612",
          "answer": 4388
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n10000 - 3297",
          "answer": 6703
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "All from 9 last from 10 : \n\n10000 - 2468",
          "answer": 7532
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n73 + 8",
          "answer": 81
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n98 + 7",
          "answer": 105
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n94 + 6",
          "answer": 100
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n89 + 7",
          "answer": 96
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Single Digit Addition : \n\n95 + 7",
          "answer": 102
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n85 + 22",
          "answer": 107
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n79 + 65",
          "answer": 144
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n94 + 79",
          "answer": 173
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n97 + 23",
          "answer": 120
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Double Digit Addition : \n\n77 + 65",
          "answer": 142
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n75 | 65",
          "answer": 815
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n98 | 73",
          "answer": 1053
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n34 | 33",
          "answer": 363
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n25 | 52",
          "answer": 302
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n72 | 87",
          "answer": 807
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n13 | 17 | 23",
          "answer": 1493
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n19 | 17 | 29",
          "answer": 1099
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n27 | 19 | 29",
          "answer": 2919
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n86 | 27 | 65",
          "answer": 8935
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Balancing Rule : \n\n15 | 07 | 15",
          "answer": 1585
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n14 x 12",
          "answer": 168
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n17 x 16",
          "answer": 272
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n12 x 17",
          "answer": 204
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n18 x 19",
          "answer": 342
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n11 x 14",
          "answer": 154
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n12 x 18",
          "answer": 216
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n19 x 15",
          "answer": 285
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n12 x 12",
          "answer": 144
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n13 x 14",
          "answer": 182
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Teens x Teens : \n\n17 x 19",
          "answer": 323
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Vedic Math (SAN) Practice Paper 2",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "vedic",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n143",
          "answer": 857
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n429",
          "answer": 571
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n662",
          "answer": 338
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n685",
          "answer": 315
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "write the compliment : \n\n584",
          "answer": 416
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n731 x 5",
          "answer": 3655
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n845 x 5",
          "answer": 4225
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n8543 x 5",
          "answer": 42715
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n86434 x 5",
          "answer": 432170
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 5 : \n\n494949 x 5",
          "answer": 2474745
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n784388 x 25",
          "answer": 19609700
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n6347 x 25",
          "answer": 158675
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n5416 x 25",
          "answer": 135400
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n4317 x 25",
          "answer": 107925
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 25 : \n\n4817 x 25",
          "answer": 120425
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n7873 x 125",
          "answer": 984125
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n6654 x 125",
          "answer": 831750
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n6511 x 125",
          "answer": 813875
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n7273 x 125",
          "answer": 909125
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Power of 125 : \n\n548644 x 125",
          "answer": 68580500
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n13 x 17",
          "answer": 221
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n34 x 36",
          "answer": 1224
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n42 x 48",
          "answer": 2016
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n65 x 65",
          "answer": 4225
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method : \n\n27 x 23",
          "answer": 621
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n36 x 76",
          "answer": 2736
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n64 x 44",
          "answer": 2816
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n56 x 56",
          "answer": 3136
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n92 x 12",
          "answer": 1104
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "L Method : \n\n39 x 79",
          "answer": 3081
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n8.4 x 8.6",
          "answer": 72.24
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n8.2 x 8.8",
          "answer": 72.16
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n2.7 x 2.3",
          "answer": 6.21
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n9.4 x 9.6",
          "answer": 90.24
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rule Method - Decimal : \n\n6.3 x 6.7",
          "answer": 42.21
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n3",
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n8",
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n7",
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n4",
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (10 Base) : \n\n1",
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n3",
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n1",
          "answer": 8
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n7",
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n6",
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Find the Complement Number (9 Base) : \n\n5",
          "answer": 4
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Vedic Math -- Practice Paper 2",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "vedic",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n87 + 79 + 8",
          "answer": 174
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n38 + 97 + 6",
          "answer": 141
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n29 + 78 + 8",
          "answer": 115
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n95 + 67 + 9",
          "answer": 171
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n17 + 48 + 9",
          "answer": 74
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n387 + 898 + 87",
          "answer": 1372
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n599 + 898 + 398",
          "answer": 1895
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n497 + 389 + 898",
          "answer": 1784
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n797 + 878 + 499",
          "answer": 2174
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Addition : \n\n488 + 197 + 89",
          "answer": 774
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n7.9 + 2.8 + 0.9 + 0.7 + 0.3",
          "answer": 12.6
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n1.5 + 4.9 + 3.4 + 1.8 + 5.0",
          "answer": 16.6
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n8.8 + 2.9 + 7.9 + 2.7 + 0.7",
          "answer": 23.0
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n3.5 + 7.7 + 3.4 + 2.1 + 5.3",
          "answer": 53.5
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n9.4 + 5.1 + 4.3 + 2.1 + 3.4",
          "answer": 24.3
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n7.55 + 2.10 + 1.43 + 4.56 + 2.61",
          "answer": 18.25
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n5.66 + 2.66 + 2.34 + 1.46 + 0.87",
          "answer": 12.99
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n2.45 + 9.65 + 0.24 + 2.97 + 1.42",
          "answer": 16.73
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n8.98 + 4.34 + 1.45 + 1.55 + 1.60",
          "answer": 17.92
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Decimal Addition : \n\n4.35 + 2.24 + 5.32 + 3.87 + 2.23",
          "answer": 18.01
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n8241 - 4991",
          "answer": 3250
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n9630 - 1880",
          "answer": 7750
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n5896 - 4998",
          "answer": 898
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n4513 - 1514",
          "answer": 2999
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n3750 - 1870",
          "answer": 1880
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n52471 - 17784",
          "answer": 34687
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n47586 - 17879",
          "answer": 29707
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n98176 - 89387",
          "answer": 8789
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n78769 - 59789",
          "answer": 18980
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Rapid Subtraction : \n\n89292 - 69796",
          "answer": 19496
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n39 x 11",
          "answer": 429
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n76 x 11",
          "answer": 836
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n49 x 11",
          "answer": 539
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n57 x 11",
          "answer": 627
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n271 x 11",
          "answer": 2981
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n984 x 11",
          "answer": 10824
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n594 x 11",
          "answer": 6534
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n8035 x 11",
          "answer": 88385
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n1817 x 11",
          "answer": 19987
        },
        {
          "type": "fill",
          "question": "Multiplication of 11 : \n\n4968 x 11",
          "answer": 54648
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "BFB 1 -- Practise Paper 1",
      "time": 8,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n1\n-1\n1\n1",
          "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n2\n-1\n1\n-1",
          "options": [2, 3, 1, 4],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n3\n-2\n2\n1",
          "options": [3, 4, 2, 1],
          "answer": 4
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n1\n-1\n1\n3",
          "options": [1, 2, 5, 4],
          "answer": 4
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n4\n-1\n1\n-1",
          "options": [4, 1, 3, 2],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n4\n-2\n2\n-3",
          "options": [4, 6, 2, 1],
          "answer": 1
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n3\n-3\n2\n1",
          "options": [3, 2, 5, 1],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n2\n-2\n3\n-1",
          "options": [2, 0, 3, 1],
          "answer": 2
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n2\n2\n-4\n4",
          "options": [2, 5, 1, 4],
          "answer": 4
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n1\n3\n-3\n2",
          "options": [1, 3, 5, 2],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n4\n-4\n1\n2",
          "options": [4, 1, 3, 2],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n4\n-3\n-1\n4",
          "options": [3, 9, 1, 4],
          "answer": 4
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n7\n-1\n-5\n2",
          "options": [7, 5, 3, 2],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n5\n4\n-7\n1",
          "options": [5, 4, 3, 1],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n1\n6\n-5\n2",
          "options": [1, 6, 3, 4],
          "answer": 4
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "BFB 1 -- Practice Paper 2",
      "time": 8,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n1\n-1\n1\n3",
          "options": [0, 1, 3, 4],
          "answer": 4
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n1\n1\n1\n-3",
          "options": [0, 2, 1, -1],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n1\n2\n-1\n-1",
          "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n2\n-3\n1\n3",
          "options": [3, 1, 2, 4],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n2\n1\n-2\n1",
          "options": [2, 3, 1, 0],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n3\n2\n-2\n1",
          "options": [2, 3, 5, 4],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n3\n-1\n-1\n1",
          "options": [3, 4, 2, 1],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n3\n-2\n-5\n6",
          "options": [3, 4, 6, 5],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n4\n-1\n2\n2",
          "options": [3, 4, 5, 6],
          "answer": 4
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n4\n2\n-1\n3",
          "options": [2, 3, 4, 5],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n4\n-3\n5\n2",
          "options": [3, 5, 4, 6],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n5\n2\n-1\n4",
          "options": [3, 2, 5, 6],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n7\n-2\n2\n6",
          "options": [6, 7, 8, 9],
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n9\n-4\n1\n5",
          "options": [6, 7, 5, 3],
          "answer": 6
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "BFB 2 -- Practise Paper 1",
      "time": 10,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n3\n-3\n1\n2",
          "options": [3, 7, 1, 2],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n2\n2\n-1\n-1",
          "options": [7, 2, 3, 8],
          "answer": 2
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n3\n1\n-4\n4",
          "options": [3, 1, 5, 4],
          "answer": 4
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n3\n1\n-3\n3",
          "options": [3, 5, 1, 4],
          "answer": 4
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n9\n-4\n-5\n2",
          "options": [9, 4, 5, 2],
          "answer": 2
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n6\n-5\n-1\n9",
          "options": [6, 5, 1, 9],
          "answer": 9
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n5\n4\n-9\n5",
          "options": [4, 5, 9, 1],
          "answer": 5
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n1\n2\n-3\n9",
          "options": [1, 2, 3, 9],
          "answer": 9
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n7\n-6\n1\n5",
          "options": [7, 6, 1, 3],
          "answer": 7
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n7\n1\n-2\n1",
          "options": [7, 3, 2, 1],
          "answer": 7
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n1\n1\n2\n5",
          "options": [1, 0, 2, 9],
          "answer": 9
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n2\n5\n-6\n8",
          "options": [2, 5, 6, 9],
          "answer": 9
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n20\n20\n-10\n-10",
          "options": [20, 12, 10, 30],
          "answer": 20
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n20\n-10\n-10\n20",
          "options": [20, 10, 22, 14],
          "answer": 20
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n30\n-10\n20\n-20",
          "options": [30, 10, 20, 14],
          "answer": 20
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n40\n-10\n-10\n20",
          "options": [43, 10, 40, 20],
          "answer": 40
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n40\n-20\n-10\n10",
          "options": [40, 20, 30, 10],
          "answer": 20
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n30\n-20\n30\n-30",
          "options": [22, 20, 30, 10],
          "answer": 10
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n40\n-20\n-10\n20",
          "options": [40, 20, 30, 12],
          "answer": 30
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n30\n-20\n-10\n10",
          "options": [30, 10, 20, 16],
          "answer": 10
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "BFB 2 -- Practice Paper 2",
      "time": 10,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n2\n1\n-3\n1",
          "options": [1, 2, 3, 4],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n4\n-3\n2\n1",
          "options": [4, 3, 5, 6],
          "answer": 4
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n3\n-2\n3\n-2",
          "options": [2, 3, 4, 1],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n2\n-2\n4\n-3",
          "options": [1, 2, 5, 0],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n7\n-6\n8\n-4",
          "options": [1, 5, 4, 7],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n5\n4\n-8\n6",
          "options": [7, 6, 5, 8],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n6\n3\n-8\n7",
          "options": [8, 7, 6, 9],
          "answer": 8
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n2\n-1\n8\n-5",
          "options": [4, 6, 7, 5],
          "answer": 4
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n8\n1\n-9\n6",
          "options": [6, 5, 4, 6],
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n6\n-5\n8\n-7",
          "options": [2, 3, 4, 2],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n8\n-2\n1\n-5",
          "options": [2, 0, 3, 4],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n5\n2\n-1\n-8",
          "options": [1, 0, 2, 3],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n50\n10\n-20\n20",
          "options": [80, 60, 50, 70],
          "answer": 80
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n10\n70\n-20\n10",
          "options": [70, 50, 60, 90],
          "answer": 70
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n20\n20\n-30\n60",
          "options": [70, 60, 50, 80],
          "answer": 70
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n80\n10\n-70\n10",
          "options": [50, 40, 30, 50],
          "answer": 50
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n40\n50\n-50\n-20",
          "options": [30, 40, 60, 70],
          "answer": 30
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n70\n-60\n10\n10",
          "options": [80, 90, 70, 60],
          "answer": 70
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Combination -- Practise Paper 1",
      "time": 10,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n2\n-2\n4\n-3",
          "options": [1, 2, 4, 3],
          "answer": 1
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n4\n-2\n1\n-2",
          "options": [4, 2, 7, 1],
          "answer": 1
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n5\n2\n-5\n1",
          "options": [3, 2, 5, 1],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n6\n-1\n2\n1",
          "options": [6, 7, 8, 1],
          "answer": 8
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n7\n-6\n8\n-4",
          "options": [7, 5, 8, 4],
          "answer": 5
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n8\n-2\n3\n-5",
          "options": [8, 2, 3, 4],
          "answer": 4
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n9\n-4\n-5\n2",
          "options": [9, 4, 5, 2],
          "answer": 2
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n6\n-5\n8\n-7",
          "options": [6, 5, 2, 7],
          "answer": 2
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n9\n-7\n-2\n8",
          "options": [9, 7, 2, 8],
          "answer": 8
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n4\n-2\n6\n-3",
          "options": [4, 2, 5, 3],
          "answer": 5
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n7\n-1\n-6\n9",
          "options": [7, 1, 6, 9],
          "answer": 9
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n6\n2\n-7\n5",
          "options": [6, 2, 7, 8],
          "answer": 6
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n10\n20\n50\n-60",
          "options": [10, 25, 50, 20],
          "answer": 20
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n70\n-20\n30\n-80",
          "options": [70, 0, 30, 8],
          "answer": 0
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n90\n-70\n60\n-50",
          "options": [30, 70, 60, 50],
          "answer": 30
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n12\n25\n-32\n41",
          "options": [12, 25, 32, 46],
          "answer": 46
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n11\n22\n-12\n15",
          "options": [11, 36, 12, 15],
          "answer": 36
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n22\n-22\n34\n-21",
          "options": [22, 12, 13, 21],
          "answer": 13
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n13\n16\n-17\n16",
          "options": [13, 16, 17, 28],
          "answer": 28
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n19\n-18\n17\n-16",
          "options": [19, 18, 2, 16],
          "answer": 2
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Combination -- Practise Paper 2",
      "time": 10,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n2\n1\n-2\n2",
          "options": [3, 5, 1, 2],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n6\n-5\n2\n6",
          "options": [9, 7, 5, 6],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n7\n-6\n1\n5",
          "options": [7, 6, 3, 7],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n9\n-7\n5\n1",
          "options": [8, 5, 6, 4],
          "answer": 8
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n6\n2\n-7\n5",
          "options": [6, 0, 1, 2],
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n6\n3\n-4\n-5",
          "options": [0, 5, 3, 1],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n6\n-2\n4\n-3",
          "options": [5, 7, 1, 5],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n4\n2\n-4\n-3",
          "options": [5, 6, 7, 8],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n9\n-7\n5\n-6",
          "options": [7, 0, 2, 1],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n8\n-6\n1\n1",
          "options": [8, 0, 6, 7],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n5\n-8\n2\n3",
          "options": [5, 3, 2, 7],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n5\n-1\n1\n-10",
          "options": [60, 80, 3, 60],
          "answer": 60
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n20\n60\n-10\n-80",
          "options": [30, 80, 20, 80],
          "answer": 80
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n30\n70\n-50\n-70",
          "options": [30, 90, 70, 80],
          "answer": 30
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n90\n10\n-80\n-27",
          "options": [43, 50, 70, 43],
          "answer": 43
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n14\n55\n-52\n30",
          "options": [47, 44, 46, 47],
          "answer": 47
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n11\n33\n5\n-49",
          "options": [0, 6, 7, 0],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n38\n-22\n-10\n41",
          "options": [47, 45, 55, 47],
          "answer": 47
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n26\n21\n-37\n12",
          "options": [22, 23, 27, 22],
          "answer": 22
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Advance 1 Paper A",
      "time": 10,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n5\n1\n2\n-7",
          "options": [1, 9, 2, 7],
          "answer": 1
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n6\n3\n-3\n2",
          "options": [6, 3, 7, 8],
          "answer": 8
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n8\n-5\n6\n-2",
          "options": [7, 5, 6, 2],
          "answer": 7
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n7\n-1\n3\n-5",
          "options": [7, 1, 4, 5],
          "answer": 4
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n6\n3\n-7\n-1",
          "options": [6, 3, 7, 1],
          "answer": 1
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n4\n-4\n8\n-5",
          "options": [4, 1, 3, 5],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n9\n-4\n-5\n6",
          "options": [9, 4, 5, 6],
          "answer": 6
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n8\n1\n-7\n1",
          "options": [8, 1, 7, 3],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n20\n-10\n-10\n40",
          "options": [20, 10, 17, 40],
          "answer": 40
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n70\n-60\n80\n-30",
          "options": [70, 20, 60, 30],
          "answer": 60
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n90\n-10\n10\n-70",
          "options": [20, 50, 10, 70],
          "answer": 20
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n28\n51\n-66\n15",
          "options": [28, 51, 66, 15],
          "answer": 28
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n82\n-61\n55\n21",
          "options": [82, 61, 97, 21],
          "answer": 97
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n37\n50\n10\n-85",
          "options": [37, 12, 10, 85],
          "answer": 12
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n88\n11\n-77\n66",
          "options": [88, 11, 77, 66],
          "answer": 88
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n45\n53\n-60\n-11",
          "options": [45, 27, 60, 11],
          "answer": 27
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n35\n51\n12\n-95",
          "options": [3, 51, 12, 95],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n21\n55\n-61\n24",
          "options": [21, 55, 39, 24],
          "answer": 39
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n49\n-32\n62\n-55",
          "options": [49, 24, 62, 55],
          "answer": 24
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n31\n55\n-36\n11",
          "options": [31, 55, 36, 61],
          "answer": 61
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Advance 1 Paper B",
      "time": 10,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n8\n-7\n6\n1",
          "options": [8, 7, 6, 1],
          "answer": 8
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n6\n3\n-6\n5",
          "options": [6, 3, 7, 8],
          "answer": 8
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n4\n-1\n6\n-9",
          "options": [0, 1, 6, 9],
          "answer": 0
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n8\n1\n-7\n5",
          "options": [8, 1, 7, 5],
          "answer": 7
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n9\n-3\n2\n-6",
          "options": [9, 3, 2, 6],
          "answer": 2
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n90\n-80\n70\n10",
          "options": [90, 80, 70, 10],
          "answer": 90
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n70\n-60\n80\n-30",
          "options": [70, 30, 80, 60],
          "answer": 60
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n21\n2\n-3\n20",
          "options": [21, 2, 40, 20],
          "answer": 40
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n44\n55\n-15\n10",
          "options": [44, 55, 15, 94],
          "answer": 94
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n22\n22\n55\n-22",
          "options": [22, 77, 55, 52],
          "answer": 77
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n62\n27\n-33\n-51",
          "options": [62, 27, 33, 5],
          "answer": 5
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n78\n-25\n46\n-4",
          "options": [78, 25, 46, 95],
          "answer": 95
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n36\n52\n-71\n81",
          "options": [36, 52, 98, 81],
          "answer": 98
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n99\n-71\n60\n-32",
          "options": [99, 71, 60, 56],
          "answer": 56
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n34\n65\n-88\n22",
          "options": [34, 65, 88, 33],
          "answer": 33
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n85\n12\n-66\n52",
          "options": [85, 12, 83, 52],
          "answer": 83
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n36\n52\n-77\n61",
          "options": [36, 72, 77, 61],
          "answer": 72
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n84\n-72\n66\n-75",
          "options": [84, 72, 3, 10],
          "answer": 3
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n38\n-25\n10\n76",
          "options": [38, 25, 10, 99],
          "answer": 99
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n32\n57\n-11\n-65",
          "options": [32, 13, 11, 65],
          "answer": 13
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Advance 1 - Paper A - Practice Paper 2",
      "time": 10,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n7\n-1\n-5\n2",
          "options": [3, 4, 5, 6],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n5\n3\n-7\n7",
          "options": [6, 7, 8, 9],
          "answer": 8
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n9\n-3\n-5\n6",
          "options": [5, 6, 7, 8],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n4\n-3\n7\n-8",
          "options": [0, 1, 2, 3],
          "answer": 0
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n8\n-6\n2\n5",
          "options": [7, 8, 9, 10],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n9\n-7\n5\n-6",
          "options": [0, 1, 2, 3],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n9\n-6\n5\n1",
          "options": [7, 8, 9, 10],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n6\n2\n-7\n6",
          "options": [6, 7, 8, 9],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n7\n-6\n8\n-5",
          "options": [3, 4, 5, 6],
          "answer": 4
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n9\n-3\n-5\n6",
          "options": [6, 7, 8, 9],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n18\n50\n11\n-23",
          "options": [56, 54, 57, 59],
          "answer": 56
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n31\n15\n-25\n55",
          "options": [76, 77, 78, 79],
          "answer": 76
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n24\n50\n15\n-53",
          "options": [34, 35, 36, 37],
          "answer": 36
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n18\n21\n-33\n12",
          "options": [17, 18, 19, 20],
          "answer": 18
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n13\n25\n51\n-10",
          "options": [78, 79, 80, 81],
          "answer": 79
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n21\n55\n-61\n24",
          "options": [38, 39, 40, 41],
          "answer": 39
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n31\n15\n-35\n22",
          "options": [31, 32, 33, 34],
          "answer": 33
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n37\n50\n10\n-85",
          "options": [11, 12, 13, 14],
          "answer": 12
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n52\n46\n-37\n-50",
          "options": [9, 10, 11, 12],
          "answer": 11
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "Solve this:\n68\n10\n-21\n-52",
          "options": [4, 5, 6, 7],
          "answer": 5
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Advance 1 - Paper B Practice 2",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n2\n-1\n-6\n1",
          "options": [4, 2, 1, 3],
          "answer": 4
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n9\n-6\n5\n-7",
          "options": [1, 2, 3, 9],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n7\n2\n-8\n6",
          "options": [7, 1, 3, 8],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n9\n-8\n5\n-5",
          "options": [2, 3, 4, 8],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n9\n-10\n-7\n5",
          "options": [3, 5, 2, 2],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n80\n30\n-50\n70",
          "options": [90, 50, 60, 70],
          "answer": 90
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n50\n10\n-70\n60",
          "options": [70, 60, 50, 70],
          "answer": 70
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n34\n-21\n-10\n11",
          "options": [34, 21, 10, 34],
          "answer": 34
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n52\n35\n-66\n20",
          "options": [41, 52, 20, 15],
          "answer": 41
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n92\n-80\n65\n11",
          "options": [88, 95, 70, 88],
          "answer": 88
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n48\n50\n-37\n15",
          "options": [76, 75, 74, 76],
          "answer": 76
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n69\n-58\n72\n16",
          "options": [99, 80, 85, 99],
          "answer": 99
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n82\n-11\n-21\n45",
          "options": [95, 70, 85, 95],
          "answer": 95
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n94\n-71\n66\n-79",
          "options": [10, 20, 15, 10],
          "answer": 10
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n36\n63\n-78\n25",
          "options": [46, 25, 30, 46],
          "answer": 46
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n97\n-56\n-30\n65",
          "options": [76, 70, 75, 76],
          "answer": 76
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n49\n-33\n81\n-26",
          "options": [71, 60, 65, 71],
          "answer": 71
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n73\n-63\n15\n52",
          "options": [77, 75, 70, 77],
          "answer": 77
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n38\n-25\n56\n10",
          "options": [79, 80, 75, 79],
          "answer": 79
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n82\n-31\n45\n-91",
          "options": [5, 10, 15, 5],
          "answer": 5
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Advance 2",
      "time": 10,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n75\n12\n-35\n22",
          "options": [75, 12, 35, 74],
          "answer": 74
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n77\n-22\n10\n-55",
          "options": [77, 22, 30, 10],
          "answer": 10
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n57\n-55\n26\n21",
          "options": [57, 55, 49, 21],
          "answer": 49
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n52\n42\n-12\n15",
          "options": [52, 97, 12, 15],
          "answer": 97
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n42\n51\n-12\n-60",
          "options": [21, 51, 12, 60],
          "answer": 21
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n453\n-301\n525\n200",
          "options": [877, 301, 525, 200],
          "answer": 877
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n250\n210\n520\n-610",
          "options": [250, 210, 370, 610],
          "answer": 370
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n225\n254\n-277\n211",
          "options": [225, 413, 277, 211],
          "answer": 413
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n556\n242\n-698\n712",
          "options": [556, 242, 698, 812],
          "answer": 812
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n534\n115\n250\n-677",
          "options": [534, 115, 222, 677],
          "answer": 222
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n39\n-26\n43\n31",
          "options": [39, 26, 87, 31],
          "answer": 87
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n68\n-57\n43\n21",
          "options": [68, 57, 43, 75],
          "answer": 75
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n62\n33\n-85\n47",
          "options": [62, 33, 85, 57],
          "answer": 57
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n93\n3\n-75\n34",
          "options": [93, 55, 75, 34],
          "answer": 55
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n62\n33\n-75\n39",
          "options": [62, 59, 75, 39],
          "answer": 59
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n88\n-66\n12\n21",
          "options": [88, 66, 12, 55],
          "answer": 55
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n66\n31\n-75\n45",
          "options": [66, 31, 75, 67],
          "answer": 67
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n77\n-30\n22\n-33",
          "options": [36, 30, 22, 33],
          "answer": 36
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n36\n21\n-31\n-13",
          "options": [36, 21, 31, 13],
          "answer": 13
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n42\n14\n-32\n60",
          "options": [42, 84, 32, 60],
          "answer": 84
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n88\n-43\n92\n81",
          "options": [88, 43, 218, 81],
          "answer": 218
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n64\n43\n31\n95",
          "options": [233, 43, 31, 95],
          "answer": 233
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n72\n11\n34\n92",
          "options": [72, 11, 209, 92],
          "answer": 209
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n56\n52\n61\n40",
          "options": [56, 52, 61, 209],
          "answer": 209
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n93\n24\n92\n80",
          "options": [289, 24, 92, 80],
          "answer": 289
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Advance 2 Practice 2",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n62\n27\n-33\n-51",
          "options": [
            62,
            27,
            5,
            51
          ],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n78\n-25\n46\n-4",
          "options": [
            95,
            78,
            46,
            4
          ],
          "answer": 95
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n36\n52\n-71\n81",
          "options": [
            36,
            98,
            52,
            71
          ],
          "answer": 98
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n99\n-71\n60\n-32",
          "options": [
            99,
            56,
            71,
            32
          ],
          "answer": 56
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n34\n65\n-88\n22",
          "options": [
            34,
            65,
            33,
            88
          ],
          "answer": 33
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n621\n-500\n153\n120",
          "options": [
            621,
            394,
            153,
            120
          ],
          "answer": 394
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n989\n-525\n30\n500",
          "options": [
            989,
            994,
            525,
            30
          ],
          "answer": 994
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n878\n-728\n621\n122",
          "options": [
            878,
            893,
            728,
            122
          ],
          "answer": 893
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n270\n-210\n112\n105",
          "options": [
            270,
            277,
            210,
            105
          ],
          "answer": 277
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n444\n555\n-999\n185",
          "options": [
            444,
            555,
            185,
            16
          ],
          "answer": 185
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n31\n24\n44\n-77",
          "options": [
            31,
            22,
            44,
            77
          ],
          "answer": 22
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n42\n13\n-55\n88",
          "options": [
            42,
            88,
            55,
            13
          ],
          "answer": 88
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n73\n22\n-50\n13",
          "options": [
            73,
            22,
            58,
            50
          ],
          "answer": 58
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n26\n33\n-5\n11",
          "options": [
            26,
            33,
            65,
            11
          ],
          "answer": 65
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n98\n-67\n23\n43",
          "options": [
            98,
            67,
            97,
            43
          ],
          "answer": 97
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n66\n-65\n-78\n44",
          "options": [
            66,
            95,
            65,
            78
          ],
          "answer": 95
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n87\n-64\n32\n41",
          "options": [
            87,
            55,
            64,
            41
          ],
          "answer": 55
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n87\n-33\n64\n-76",
          "options": [
            87,
            11,
            33,
            76
          ],
          "answer": 11
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n47\n-64\n75\n-69",
          "options": [
            47,
            20,
            64,
            75
          ],
          "answer": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n98\n-64\n53\n-71",
          "options": [
            98,
            16,
            64,
            53
          ],
          "answer": 16
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n72\n-61\n57\n55",
          "options": [
            123,
            72,
            61,
            55
          ],
          "answer": 123
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n29\n75\n84\n45",
          "options": [
            29,
            213,
            75,
            45
          ],
          "answer": 213
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n86\n95\n18\n55",
          "options": [
            86,
            244,
            95,
            18
          ],
          "answer": 244
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n67\n55\n52\n55",
          "options": [
            67,
            229,
            55,
            52
          ],
          "answer": 229
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n83\n56\n-25\n77",
          "options": [
            83,
            191,
            56,
            77
          ],
          "answer": 191
        }
      ]
    } ,
    {
      "title": "Advance 3",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n34\n-22\n56\n-50",
          "options": [34, 28, 18, 50],
          "answer": 18
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n99\n-55\n50\n-30",
          "options": [99, 64, 67, 55],
          "answer": 64
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n67\n21\n-55\n15",
          "options": [73, 48, 15, 52],
          "answer": 48
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n130\n219\n50\n-277",
          "options": [950, 122, 240, 940],
          "answer": 122
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n666\n-511\n222\n-66",
          "options": [490, 311, 810, 260],
          "answer": 311
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n448\n-321\n572\n-80",
          "options": [380, 250, 619, 790],
          "answer": 619
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n87\n-65\n32\n41",
          "options": [95, 71, 34, 78],
          "answer": 95
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n23\n42\n-60\n84",
          "options": [48, 89, 55, 32],
          "answer": 89
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n36\n-25\n23\n43",
          "options": [62, 33, 85, 77],
          "answer": 77
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n22\n14\n21\n-13",
          "options": [59, 20, 44, 34],
          "answer": 44
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n63\n33\n-62\n15",
          "options": [49, 88, 84, 32],
          "answer": 49
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n24\n12\n23\n-16",
          "options": [98, 32, 43, 31],
          "answer": 43
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n33\n75\n51\n50",
          "options": [36, 14, 44, 209],
          "answer": 209
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n68\n15\n56\n55",
          "options": [97, 283, 59, 194],
          "answer": 194
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n75\n41\n79\n55",
          "options": [66, 250, 32, 12],
          "answer": 250
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n64\n26\n70\n-87",
          "options": [73, 98, 21, 34],
          "answer": 73
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n21\n35\n-18\n61",
          "options": [31, 99, 151, 43],
          "answer": 99
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n34\n56\n78\n-91",
          "options": [42, 92, 77, 85],
          "answer": 77
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n38\n58\n66\n73",
          "options": [178, 54, 235, 35],
          "answer": 235
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n63\n36\n72\n60",
          "options": [74, 231, 240, 62],
          "answer": 231
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n34\n43\n76\n59",
          "options": [37, 56, 212, 164],
          "answer": 212
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this: \n\n46 x 7",
          "options": [320, 222, 322, 121],
          "answer": 322
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n\n64 x 9",
          "options": [576, 810, 282, 124],
          "answer": 576
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n\n38 x 7",
          "options": [371, 256, 212, 266],
          "answer": 266
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n\n65 x 3",
          "options": [34, 195, 92, 16],
          "answer": 195
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n\n75 x 9",
          "options": [3, 510, 55, 675],
          "answer": 675
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n\n32 x 3",
          "options": [371, 96, 12, 64],
          "answer": 96
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n\n65 x 8",
          "options": [321, 562, 520, 14],
          "answer": 520
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n\n24 x 8",
          "options": [192, 256, 22, 16],
          "answer": 192
        },
        { "type": "multiple_choice", "question":
        "solve this:\n\n53 x 9",
          "options": [521, 202, 621, 477],
          "answer": 477
        }

      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Advance 3 -- Practice Paper--2",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n94\n-71\n66\n-79",
          "options": [10, 20, 30, 40],
          "answer": 10
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n36\n63\n-78\n25",
          "options": [46, 56, 66, 76],
          "answer": 46
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n97\n-56\n-30\n65",
          "options": [66, 76, 86, 96],
          "answer": 76
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n666\n-511\n222\n-66",
          "options": [311, 411, 511, 611],
          "answer": 311
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n448\n-321\n572\n-80",
          "options": [519, 619, 719, 819],
          "answer": 619
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n339\n-125\n750\n-500",
          "options": [439, 464, 489, 514],
          "answer": 464
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n97\n-66\n24\n13",
          "options": [68, 78, 88, 98],
          "answer": 68
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n78\n-55\n32\n44",
          "options": [89, 99, 109, 119],
          "answer": 99
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n24\n31\n-55\n87",
          "options": [67, 77, 87, 97],
          "answer": 87
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n48\n-34\n73\n-51",
          "options": [26, 36, 46, 56],
          "answer": 36
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n38\n-24\n71\n-65",
          "options": [10, 20, 30, 40],
          "answer": 20
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n97\n-65\n54\n-12",
          "options": [64, 74, 84, 94],
          "answer": 74
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n45\n61\n30\n72",
          "options": [208, 218, 228, 238],
          "answer": 208
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n88\n-43\n92\n81",
          "options": [198, 208, 218, 228],
          "answer": 218
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n64\n43\n31\n95",
          "options": [223, 233, 243, 253],
          "answer": 233
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n21\n92\n-54\n51",
          "options": [100, 110, 120, 130],
          "answer": 110
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n13\n98\n-21\n34",
          "options": [104, 114, 124, 134],
          "answer": 124
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n54\n21\n-99\n54",
          "options": [10, 20, 30, 40],
          "answer": 30
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n62\n61\n37\n80",
          "options": [40, 50, 60, 70],
          "answer": 40
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n56\n74\n35\n60",
          "options": [215, 225, 235, 245],
          "answer": 225
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n64\n84\n10\n90",
          "options": [228, 238, 248, 258],
          "answer": 248
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n84 x 3",
          "options": [252, 362, 472, 582],
          "answer": 252
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n27 x 4",
          "options": [108, 118, 128, 138],
          "answer": 108
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n52 x 6",
          "options": [312, 322, 332, 342],
          "answer": 312
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n33 x 4",
          "options": [122, 132, 142, 152],
          "answer": 132
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n65 x 5",
          "options": [325, 335, 345, 355],
          "answer": 325
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n85 x 7",
          "options": [585, 595, 605, 615],
          "answer": 595
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n73 x 8",
          "options": [574, 584, 594, 604],
          "answer": 584
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n94 x 9",
          "options": [836, 846, 856, 866],
          "answer": 846
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n28 x 2",
          "options": [46, 52, 56, 62],
          "answer": 56
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Advance 4 Practice Paper 1",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n750\n140\n-220\n310",
          "options": [
            750,
            340,
            130,
            980
          ],
          "answer": 980
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n460\n520\n-870\n230",
          "options": [
            460,
            340,
            130,
            340
          ],
          "answer": 340
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n350\n120\n510\n-850",
          "options": [
            130,
            980,
            350,
            510
          ],
          "answer": 130
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n530\n250\n-660\n770",
          "options": [
            130,
            890,
            530,
            250
          ],
          "answer": 890
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n280\n610\n-870\n960",
          "options": [
            980,
            280,
            960,
            980
          ],
          "answer": 980
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n840\n-720\n650\n200",
          "options": [
            840,
            970,
            650,
            980
          ],
          "answer": 970
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n39\n30\n-58\n34",
          "options": [
            45,
            86,
            39,
            30
          ],
          "answer": 45
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n66\n-56\n43\n33",
          "options": [
            66,
            86,
            43,
            97
          ],
          "answer": 86
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n97\n-85\n33\n52",
          "options": [
            97,
            85,
            33,
            97
          ],
          "answer": 97
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n39\n-28\n74\n-61",
          "options": [
            24,
            39,
            28,
            97
          ],
          "answer": 24
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n88\n-12\n-62\n71",
          "options": [
            85,
            86,
            12,
            62
          ],
          "answer": 85
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n99\n-88\n84\n-63",
          "options": [
            32,
            99,
            88,
            97
          ],
          "answer": 32
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n68\n54\n73\n82",
          "options": [
            277,
            128,
            98,
            73
          ],
          "answer": 277
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n98\n74\n76\n63",
          "options": [
            261,
            277,
            63,
            261
          ],
          "answer": 261
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n59\n46\n54\n18",
          "options": [
            177,
            46,
            59,
            177
          ],
          "answer": 177
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n33\n37\n59\n-46",
          "options": [
            33,
            83,
            46,
            83
          ],
          "answer": 83
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n21\n96\n-73\n84",
          "options": [
            128,
            128,
            77,
            127
          ],
          "answer": 128
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n34\n56\n78\n-91",
          "options": [
            32,
            77,
            56,
            77
          ],
          "answer": 77
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n46 x 7",
          "options": [
            322,
            220,
            120,
            322
          ],
          "answer": 322
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n44 x 5",
          "options": [
            220,
            244,
            320,
            220
          ],
          "answer": 220
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n75 x 2",
          "options": [
            150,
            120,
            130,
            150
          ],
          "answer": 150
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n91 x 3",
          "options": [
            273,
            371,
            231,
            273
          ],
          "answer": 273
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n24 x 36",
          "options": [
            864,
            820,
            768,
            864
          ],
          "answer": 864
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n52 x 49",
          "options": [
            2548,
            1948,
            2549,
            2548
          ],
          "answer": 2548
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n78 x 16",
          "options": [
            1248,
            1284,
            1247,
            1248
          ],
          "answer": 1248
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n53 x 42",
          "options": [
            2226,
            2235,
            2026,
            2226
          ],
          "answer": 2226
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n227 / 3",
          "options": [
            75,
            73,
            77,
            75
          ],
          "answer": 75
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n451 / 4",
          "options": [
            112,
            114,
            115,
            112
          ],
          "answer": 112
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n632 / 8",
          "options": [
            79,
            81,
            77,
            79
          ],
          "answer": 79
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n3927 / 8",
          "options": [
            490,
            500,
            493,
            490
          ],
          "answer": 490
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n3448 / 4",
          "options": [
            1149,
            1148,
            1147,
            1149
          ],
          "answer": 1149
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n5716 / 4",
          "options": [
            1429,
            1428,
            1427,
            1429
          ],
          "answer": 1429
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "title": "Advance 4 Practice 2",
      "time": 15,
      "paper_type": "abacus",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n880\n-120\n-560\n170",
          "options": [
            880,
            370,
            560,
            670
          ],
          "answer": 370
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n830\n110\n-820\n550",
          "options": [
            830,
            550,
            670,
            650
          ],
          "answer": 670
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n135\n650\n-600\n500",
          "options": [
            135,
            685,
            600,
            700
          ],
          "answer": 685
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n885\n-720\n631\n-500",
          "options": [
            296,
            500,
            720,
            885
          ],
          "answer": 296
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n998\n-221\n112\n-550",
          "options": [
            998,
            339,
            221,
            400
          ],
          "answer": 339
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n446\n-335\n221\n600",
          "options": [
            446,
            600,
            932,
            221
          ],
          "answer": 932
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n97\n-86\n21\n23",
          "options": [
            97,
            55,
            86,
            99
          ],
          "answer": 55
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n36\n-15\n34\n34",
          "options": [
            86,
            89,
            36,
            34
          ],
          "answer": 89
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n98\n-75\n44\n99",
          "options": [
            98,
            44,
            99,
            77
          ],
          "answer": 99
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n37\n-13\n-12\n-12",
          "options": [
            37,
            12,
            34,
            24
          ],
          "answer": 34
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n38\n-24\n32\n77",
          "options": [
            38,
            32,
            77,
            85
          ],
          "answer": 77
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n48\n-34\n-51\n36",
          "options": [
            48,
            51,
            34,
            36
          ],
          "answer": 36
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n64\n26\n70\n-81\n79",
          "options": [
            64,
            180,
            49,
            79
          ],
          "answer": 180
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n32\n14\n79\n-99\n26",
          "options": [
            32,
            53,
            26,
            131
          ],
          "answer": 131
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n15\n55\n11\n99\n180",
          "options": [
            55,
            99,
            167,
            180
          ],
          "answer": 167
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n65\n53\n42\n-76\n84",
          "options": [
            65,
            91,
            76,
            84
          ],
          "answer": 91
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n99\n91\n-72\n49\n167",
          "options": [
            167,
            128,
            76,
            99
          ],
          "answer": 128
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n76\n24\n-22\n53\n131",
          "options": [
            131,
            76,
            180,
            99
          ],
          "answer": 180
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n75\n60\n-71\n-50\n82\n96",
          "options": [
            137,
            93,
            241,
            96
          ],
          "answer": 241
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n34\n31\n-27\n74\n84\n99",
          "options": [
            65,
            99,
            166,
            118
          ],
          "answer": 99
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n31\n20\n53\n-80\n70\n166",
          "options": [
            166,
            128,
            53,
            99
          ],
          "answer": 166
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n58\n26\n53\n-52\n74\n82",
          "options": [
            66,
            128,
            93,
            96
          ],
          "answer": 93
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n59\n20\n33\n-30\n67\n78",
          "options": [
            120,
            241,
            59,
            88
          ],
          "answer": 241
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\nMultiplication\n42 x 5",
          "options": [
            210,
            220,
            230,
            240
          ],
          "answer": 210
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n86 x 8",
          "options": [
            688,
            700,
            720,
            740
          ],
          "answer": 688
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n72 x 3",
          "options": [
            216,
            224,
            230,
            240
          ],
          "answer": 216
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n55 x 39",
          "options": [
            2145,
            2150,
            2200,
            2250
          ],
          "answer": 2145
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n87 x 55",
          "options": [
            4785,
            4800,
            4900,
            5000
          ],
          "answer": 4785
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\nDivision\n672 / 6",
          "options": [
            112,
            120,
            130,
            140
          ],
          "answer": 112
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "question": "solve this:\n7642 / 3",
          "options": [
            2547,
            2600,
            2700,
            2800
          ],
          "answer": 2547
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
 
